Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Stop her!
You all lied to me.
You humiliated me.
You betrayed me.
I curse you to suffer a horrible death...
and be barred from rebirth.
(Xuanming Gate)
If there's a next life,
I'll skin you alive...
and grind your bones into ashes.
(Gemini)
(Episode 1)
Xian.
For this kind of thing,
between my cousin and me,
who do you prefer...
to do it with?
You're still thinking about that woman at this time?
What?
Have I not done well enough?
Your Highness.
His Highness has been busy...
overseeing the construction of Zhaoyue Pavilion lately.
His Highness specifically instructed us...
to send someone to find him at Zhaoyue Pavilion...
if you need anything.
You didn't have to come all the way here yourself.
I want to give him a surprise.
Bao Qin.
Just wait for me here.
Your Highness.
My dear.
Why are you here?
Your Highness has been busy with work lately.
I brought some snacks for Your Highness to try.
I don't know if you'll like them.
My dear.
The weather has been cold lately.
Your blindness makes things difficult for you.
From now on, let the servants...
do these things from now on.
You're supervising the construction...
of Zhaoyue Pavilion for my birthday.
What I'm doing is nothing by comparison.
Thank you, my dear.
My dear.
Let me help you.
What's wrong, Your Highness?
It's nothing, my dear.
I accidentally...
bumped into the corner of the table.
Your Highness.
I especially asked someone...
to get these famous snacks from Jiangnan.
I had them urgently delivered.
Your Highness.
Try it.
- Here. - Thank you, my dear.
My dear.
Did you get burned?
I'm fine.
I'm blind, so I couldn't see the candle.
That's how I accidentally burned myself.
Let me take a look.
Is it serious?
Your Highness.
I'm fine.
My dear.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell elsewhere?
I'm not unwell.
Your Highness.
Your Highness...
is going to be a father.
That's great, my dear.
I'm going to be a father.
The weather has been cold lately.
Now that you're pregnant,
you have to take care of yourself.
Let's go.
I'll take you back to your room.
Okay.
Your Highness.
What was that sound?
It's all right.
Stray cats often knock over things at night.
It's not a big deal.
Let's go.
The weather is getting colder.
It's unbearable.
Lately, there have been more and more Qiangs in the capital.
We'd better watch out.
The Qiang people?
We don't need to be afraid of the Qiang people.
Did you see this?
I can kill two at once!
Xun...
The Xuntian Sect.
(Xiao Ren)
- Let's go! - Go!
Run!
(Imperial Dovecote)
Where are you taking the weapon plans...
of the Ministry of Military Provisions?
Who are you?
I'm the guard of the Imperial City...
and the inspector of the officials.
I have special permission...
to take action without His Majesty's consent.
I am Xiao Ren of the Xuntian Sect.
Remember my name.
Send my regards to Hades.
Sis.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We are government officials when we're at work.
We are not siblings.
Yes, Master.
I've found the arms traffickers.
This is the latest information from our spies.
Wipe your face.
Liu Ying Xue...
The Princess of Chu...
A secret affair and harem infighting?
We have three spies in the Prince of Chu's manor,
yet this is all they've found out?
Situ Xian is cunning and very alert.
It's hard for our men to get close to him.
But I was thinking,
since we can't send someone in,
why don't we get someone from the inside?
Let's make use of the conflict in their home.
(The Princess of Chu is pregnant)
Tomorrow,
after we deal with the arms traffickers,
we'll look for an opportunity...
to meet this Princess of Chu.
Bao Qin.
I'm the only one...
who shall give birth to His Highness's child.
You don't deserve it.